<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<wizard>
   <caption>First-time-setup wizard</caption>
   <sections>
      <section>
         <description>Welcome screen</description>
         <name>Wizard_Welcome</name>
         <topic>MediaPortal Wizard</topic>
         <information></information>
         <header>Welcome to the first-time-setup wizard!</header>
         <body>This wizard will take you through the basic configuration steps needed to get MediaPortal up and running for the first time. Take your time to read the information on each page.</body>
         <image>wizards/wizard_fts.png</image>
      </section>
      <section>
         <description></description>
         <name>General</name>
         <topic>Language and general settings</topic>
         <information>Please select the regional display language and various general settings. It is recommended to run MediaPortal in full screen, for the best viewing experience.</information>
      </section>
      <section>
         <description></description>
         <name>Skin</name>
         <topic>Skin settings</topic>
         <information>Please select from the available installed skins the one you would like to use with MediaPortal.</information>
      </section>
      <section>
         <description></description>
         <name>Wizard_SelectPlugins</name>
         <topic>Select default plugins</topic>
         <information>Please check desired plugins you would like to be loaded automatically when MediaPortal starts.</information>
      </section>
      <section>
         <description>Picture Folders</description>
         <name>PictureShares</name>
         <topic>Picture Folders</topic>
         <information>Add Picture folders here. By checking one of the folders you will make that folder the default folder, which will be automatically shown when you enter My Pictures.</information>
         <dependency>Wizard_SelectPlugins.Plugin.MyPictures</dependency>
      </section>
      <section>
         <description>Movie Folders</description>
         <name>MovieShares</name>
         <topic>Movie Folders</topic>
         <information>Add Movie folders here. By checking one of the folders you will make that folder the default folder, which will be automatically shown when you enter My Movies.</information>
         <dependency>Wizard_SelectPlugins.Plugin.MyMovies</dependency>
      </section>
      <section>
         <description>Music Folders</description>
         <name>MusicShares</name>
         <topic>Music Folders</topic>
         <information>Add Music folders here. By checking one of the folders you will make that folder the default folder, which will be automatically shown when you enter My Music.</information>
         <dependency>Wizard_SelectPlugins.Plugin.MyMusic</dependency>
      </section>
      <section>
         <description/>
         <name>MusicDatabase</name>
         <topic>Music Database</topic>
         <information>By pressing the Update-button below, the wizard will scan for and extract music tag information from music files found in the marked folders. The tag information will be stored in MediaPortals music database, this will greatly speed up the usage of the plugin.</information>
         <dependency>MusicShares.Shares.Available</dependency>
      </section>
      <section>
         <description>Wizard done screen</description>
         <name>Wizard_Finished</name>
         <topic>Congratulations!</topic>
         <information></information>
         <header>This Modules Configuration is Complete!</header>
         <body>You have now finished the configuration of this Wizard. If at anytime, you wish to alter any of these settings, press F2 from within MediaPortal. Please consult the appropriate MediaPortal documentation for further explanation of each setting.</body>
         <image>wizards/wizard_done.png</image>
      </section>
   </sections>
</wizard>
